Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 43, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Lenin heritage, 1934; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Notes: Speech delivered by Joseph Stalin at the Second Congress of Soviets of the U.S.S.R., January 26, 1924, five days after Lenin's death
  - Item 3: Economic problems of socialism in the U. S. S. R., 1952; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The new Russian policy (June 23, 1931), Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Author: Joseph Stalin; George S. Counts
  - Item 5: In praise of learning, 1938; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Author: Joseph Stalin; V. M. Molotov
  - Item 6: The tasks of the working class in mastering the technique of production, 1932; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Notes: Speech delivered on February 4, 1931 in Moscow, at the First All-Russian Conference of Workers in Socialist Industry
- Box: 43, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The 'Penalty Awards' of Irvin Stalmaster: permanent arbitrator under agreement between the Waterfront Employers Association of The Pacific Coast and International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union., 1939; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Irvin Stalmaster
- Box: 43, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: British workers in action, 1800-1945, Publication (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Author: John Stammers
- Box: 43, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labor and the new deal., 1936; Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Author: Louis Stark
  - Item 2: Building and defending democracy, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Author: Mark Starr
  - Item 3: Labor looks at education, 1946; Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Creeping socialism vs. limping capitalism, 1954; Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Box: 43, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The church and the workers, 1931; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Author: Bennett Stevens
- Box: 43, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The new economics and world peace, 1944; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Author: Robert Stevens
- Box: 43, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Schools for tomorrow's citizens, 1939; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
    Author: Maxwell Slutz Stewart
- Box: 43, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: As I see it: observations of a civil servant. 50 essayettes of 150 words., 1941; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: Warner W. Stockberger
- Box: 44, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The collapse of American Communism, 1939; Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Author: Benjamin Stolberg
- Box: 44, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Carpetbaggers of industry, 1935; Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Author: Thomas L. Stokes
- Box: 44, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Underground in Illinois: how coal miners live, work, and struggle for Unity, 1934; Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Author: Richard Stockton
    Notes: By 100 Coal Miners and Richard Stockton.
- Box: 44, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The attitude of the Socialists toward the trade unions, 1900; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Author: N. I. Stone
    Notes: Address delivered at the National Convention of the Socialist Labor Party at Rochester, N.Y.,on March 28, 1900
- Box: 44, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Why you should be a socialist, 1938; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Author: John Strachey
- Box: 44, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Christianity in industry, Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Author: George W. Strake
    Notes: Address delivered on The Catholic Hour
- Box: 44, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Kuomintang-communist crisis in China; a first-hand account of one of the most critical periods in Far Eastern history, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Author: Anna Louise Strong
- Box: 44, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Italian intellectuals under fascism: facts and documents, 1934; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Author: Student League for Industrial Democracy (U.S.)
- Box: 44, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The American ultras; the extreme right and the military-industrial complex., 1962; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Author: Irwin Suall
- Box: 44, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The National Industrial Recovery Act, 1933; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Author: John Francis Sullivan; Andrew J. Biemiller; Maynard C. Krueger
- Box: 44, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Freedom of association and compulsory unionism in Sweden and the United States, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Author: Clyde W. Summers
- Box: 44, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Union powers and workers' rights, 1951; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Box: 44, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the American working class, 1933; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Author: Arne Swabeck
- Box: 44, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Sweating: its cause and remedy, 1894; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Our American Dreyfus case; a challenge to California justice, 1935; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Author: Lillian Symes
- Box: 44, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Michael Angelo's sonnets, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Author: John Addington Symonds
- Box: 44, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A symposium on unemployment, 1930; Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Box: 44, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The TWUA story: they said it couldnt be done., 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Box: 44, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Corruption and racketeering in the labor movement, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 18)
    Author: Philip Taft
- Box: 44, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Understanding union administration, 1946; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Judicial procedure in labor unions., 1945; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Democracy in trade unions, Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Dues and initiation fees in labor unions, 1946; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: The problem of labor relations in the Maritime Industry, Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: A rereading of Selig Perlman's, A Theory of the Labor Movement, 1950; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Strife in the Maritime Industry, 1939; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Box: 44, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Justice and freedom for industry, 1915; Publication (Box 44, Folder 20)
    Author: William H. Taft
- Box: 44, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Should women be meatcutters?: an attitudinal survey of meat wrappers and butchers on opening the field of meat cutting to women, 1972; Publication (Box 44, Folder 21)
    Author: Laurie Taub
- Box: 44, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Inside job: the story of Trotskyite intrigue in the labor movement, 1947; Publication (Box 44, Folder 22)
    Author: Herb Tank
- Box: 44, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Outlines of a theory of wages, 1915; Publication (Box 44, Folder 23)
    Author: F. W. Taussig
- Box: 44, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Effectuating the labor contract through arbitration, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 24)
    Author: George W Taylor
- Box: 44, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: A spiritual autobiography, 1950; Publication (Box 44, Folder 25)
    Author: Ordway Tead
- Box: 44, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: 60 words a minute and what do you get?: clerical workers today, 1976; Publication (Box 44, Folder 26)
    Author: Jean Teppermen
- Box: 44, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: American labor and the trade agreements, 1939; Publication (Box 44, Folder 27)
    Author: J. William Terry
- Box: 45, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Fair employment works, 1951; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Julius A. Thomas
  - Item 2: Is the New Deal socialism?: An answer to Al Smith and the American Liberty League, 1936; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Norman Thomas
  - Item 3: World federation, what are the difficulties?, 1942; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Russia--democracy or dictatorship?, 1939; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Norman Thomas; Joel Seidman
  - Item 5: Democratic socialism, a new appraisal, 1953; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The plight of the share-cropper, 1934; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Notes: Includes Report of survey made by the Memphis chapter, L. I. D. and the Tyronza socialist party under the direction of William R. Amberson.
  - Item 7: Which road for American workers, Socialist or Communist?, 1936; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Notes: Norman Thomas vs Earl Browder; debate, Madison Square Garden, New York, November 27, 1935.
  - Item 8: Shall labor support Roosevelt?, 1936; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Box: 45, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The constructive program of socialism, as illustrated by measures advanced by socialists in municipal, state and national legislation, 1908; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Author: Carl Dean Thompson
  - Item 2: Public ownership of railways, 1914; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Box: 45, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The path of a renegade: why Earl Browder was expelled from the Communist Party, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Author: Robert Thompson
- Box: 45, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The successes of the anti-fascist united front, 1935; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Author: Maurice Thorez
- Box: 45, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Communism in U.S.A., 1936; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph F. Thorning
- Box: 45, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The working class is the leading force, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Author: Timur Timofeevich Timofeev
- Box: 45, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The injunction menace, 1932; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Author: Charlotte Todes
- Box: 45, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Together we are strong, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Box: 45, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The closed shop, 1942; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Author: Jerome L. Toner; John A. Ryan
- Box: 45, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Seeking foreign trouble, 1940; Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Author: Ralph Townsend
- Box: 45, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The heritage of Gene Debs, selections, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Author: Alexander Trachtenberg
  - Item 2: Books on trial: the case of Alexander Trachtenberg, Director, International Publishers, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: History of May Day, 1937; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The history of May Day, 1935; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Box: 45, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: He said: 'Guilty', I say: frame-up!: Louis Weinstocks Story, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Box: 45, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Trade Union Unity League, affiliated to R.I.L.U.: its program, structure, methods and history, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Box: 45, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Industrial unionism, 1908; Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Author: W. E. Trautmann
  - Item 2: Direct action and sabotage, 1912; Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Box: 45, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Industry at the crossroads: a handbook on industrial relations based on the social encyclicals of Leo XIII and Pius XI, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Author: Gerald C. Treacy
  - Item 2: Labor's charter of liberty: a simplified edition of the Encyclical Rerum Novarum by Pope Leo XIII, 1943; Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: The church and social order: a reiteration of the Churchs teaching on ownership, property, labor, security, wages and establishment of social order, with discussion club outline, 1941; Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Box: 45, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Who killed Carlo Tresca?, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Author: Arturo Giovannitti; John Dos Passos
- Box: 45, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: My flight from Siberia, 1925; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
    Author: Leon Trotsky; Malcolm Campbell
- Box: 45, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The time of the toad; a study of inquisition in America by one of the Hollywood ten, 1950; Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Author: Dalton Trumbo
  - Item 2: Harry Bridges; a discussion of the latest effort to deport civil liberties and the rights of American labor, 1941; Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Box: 45, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Frocks and curls: the clothing industry and womens fashions from 1850 to 1900 in Hampshire County and vicinity, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Author: Carla Tscherny
    Notes: Exhibit at Hampshire College, Amherst, Massachusetts, April 25-29, 1978
- Box: 46, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Columbia law review, 1921; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (1921:May)
- Box: 46, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Socialism marches on in the Soviet Union, 1937; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Author: James B. Turner
- Box: 46, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Strikes and democratic government, 1947; Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Author: Twentieth Century Fund. Labor Committee
  - Item 2: Labor and national defense; a survey of the special labor problems arising from Americas defense activities and a program for action; the factual findings, 1941; Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Box: 46, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The united front, 1933; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Author: August Tyler
- Box: 46, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Jewish labor movement: a living legacy, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Author: Gus Tyler
  - Item 2: A new philosophy for labor, 1959; Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Box: 46, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The pattern of garments, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Box: 46, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Housing in Akron: some questions, some answers, Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Author: Unitarian-Universalist Church
- Box: 46, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Prospectus: fourth conclusive year issue of the five year plan in four loan, 1932; Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Author: State Bank of the U.S.S.R.
- Box: 46, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The United States and the Soviet Union, some Quaker proposals for peace, 1949; Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Author: American Friends Service Committee
- Box: 46, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Investigation of communist propaganda, 1930; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Author: United States. Congress. House. Special Committee on Communist Activities in the United States.
    Notes: Extracts from hearings before a Special Committee to Investigate Communist Activity in the United States of the House of Representatives, seventy-first Congress, third session, pursuant to H. Res. 220 providing for an investigation of communist propaganda
- Box: 46, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Subversive influence in certain industrial plants: eastern Pennsylvania, Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary
    Notes: Hearings before the Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act and Other Internal Security Laws of the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate, Eighty-third Congress, second session
  - Item 2: Investigation of Communist influence in the field of publications (March of labor), 1954; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Author: United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities
    Notes: Hearings before the Committee on Un-American Activities, House of Representatives, Eighty-third Congress, second session. July 8 and 15, 1954.
  - Item 3: 100 things you should know about communism, 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Notes: Fifth of a series on the communist conspiracy and its influence in this country as a whole on religion, on education, on labor and on our Government.
- Box: 46, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Violations of Free Speech and Rights of Labor. Part 2, 1937; Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Education and Labor
    Notes: Hearings before the United States Senate Committee on Education and Labor, pursuant to S. Res. 266, Seventy-Fifth Congress, second session, on July 22, 1937
- Box: 46, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Negro women and their jobs, 1954; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Box: 46, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The case of United States of America vs. William Z. Foster [and others] members of the National Committee of the Communist Party of the United States, 1946; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Notes: Briefs of the defendants arguing the unconstitutionality of the Smith Act and of the indictments against them thereunder.
- Box: 46, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Communism in action, 1946; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Author: Library of Congress. Legislative Reference Service
    Notes: Documented study and analysis of communism in operation in the Soviet union, prepared at the instance and under the direction of Representative Everett M. Dirksen of Illinois by the Legislative reference service of the Library of Congress under the direct
- Box: 46, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Youth, jobs and defense, 1941; Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: United States. National Youth Administration
- Box: 46, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The strike at Pullman, 1894; Publication (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Author: George Mortimer Pullman
    Notes: Statements of President Geo. M. Pullman and Second Vice-President T.H. Wickes, before the U.S. Strike Commission: also published statements of the company during the continuance of the strike.
- Box: 46, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Women at work: a century of industrial change, 1933; Publication (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Author: Eleanor Crosby Nelson
  - Item 2: Wartime reminders to women who work: the paying guest; the paid hostess, 1943; Publication (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Author: United States. Women's Bureau
- Box: 46, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Socialism and the negro problem, 1902; Publication (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Author: Charles H. Vail
- Box: 46, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The doom of the boycott, 1911; Publication (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Author: James Wallace Van Cleave
- Box: 46, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Social work, peace and the people's well-being, 1941; Publication (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Author: Mary Van Kleeck; Marion T. Hathway
- Box: 46, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Background of the Plymouth trial, Publication (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Author: Bartolomeo Vanzetti
- Box: 46, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The teamsters' campaign to smash a union, 1974; Publication (Box 46, Folder 23)
    Author: Lester Velie
- Box: 46, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Soviet trade unions today, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Author: Andrei Verbin
- Box: 46, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Chicanas speak out. Women: new voice of La Raza, 1971; Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
    Author: Mirta Vidal
- Box: 46, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Viscose story: eight years of union accomplishment in the plants of the American Viscose Corporation, Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Author: Textile Workers Union of America. Educational Dept.
- Box: 46, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Women workers: some basic statistics, 1971; Publication (Box 46, Folder 27)
    Author: Lise Vogel
- Box: 46, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Voice of America forum lectures. Automation series, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 28)
    Author: Voice of America (Organization)
- Box: 46, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Passaic, 1926; Publication (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Author: Mary Heaton Vorse
- Box: 46, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The case for the guaranteed annual wage., 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 30)
    Author: Mary Theresa Waggaman
- Box: 46, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The importance of ratifying the Federal child labor amendment, 1934; Publication (Box 46, Folder 31)
    Author: Robert F. Wagner
    Notes: Address broadcast over WJZ and associated stations, January 26, 1934.
  - Item 2: Labor disputes measure, 1935; Publication (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Box: 46, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Brief submitted by Louis Waldman on behalf of the State Committee of the Socialist Party in opposition to use of injunctions in labor disputes and in support of bill curbing its abuses, 1933; Publication (Box 46, Folder 32)
    Author: Louis Waldman
  - Item 2: Should unions be incorporated? Responsibility of unions under the law, 1937; Publication (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Food and the people: the problem of the high cost of living in the New York Legislature, 1918; Publication (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Box: 46, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Henry Wallace says 'Increase wages out of profits!', 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 33)
    Author: Henry Agard Wallace
  - Item 2: Institute of Pacific Relations: pamphlets, Publication (Box 46, Folder 33)
    Author: [Our job in the Pacific]
- Box: 47, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The triumph of Socialism: address of the Chairman R.C. Wallhead to the I.L.P. Conference, 1923; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Author: R. C. Wallhead
- Box: 47, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor-union socialism and socialist labor-unionism, 1912; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Author: William English Walling
- Box: 47, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The black flag of piracy, 1935; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Author: Mike Walsh
- Box: 47, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Welfare study, 1918; Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Author: Cecil Walton
- Box: 47, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The division of wealth: a lantern lecture, 1907; Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Wanhope
- Box: 47, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)